<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud Spanner Ecosystem </title>
    <link>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cloud Spanner Ecosystem </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/blog/</guid>
      <description>Technical overview  Apr 2020: Things I Wished More Developers Knew About Databases  Operational excellence  Oct 2020: Scaling Cloud Spanner Instances Jul 2020: Cloud Spanner Change Watcher and Cloud Spanner Change Publisher May 2020: Create Cloud Spanner Scheduled Backups Apr 2020: Instrumenting Cloud Spanner Go Applications with OpenCensus Mar 2020: Troubleshooting Cloud Spanner Applications with OpenCensus  Internals  Jan 2021: The Magic of Distributed Joins in Cloud Spanner May 2020: How Does Spanner Avoid Single Point of Failures in Writes?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Spanner Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/home/</guid>
      <description>The Cloud Spanner Ecosystem GitHub organization hosts a collection of public repositories that are owned-by and developed-for the Google Cloud Spanner user community.
All the hosted projects are based on open source contributions. We’d love for you to report issues, file feature requests, and send pull requests (see contributions). Note that none of the projects are officially supported by Google as part of the Cloud Spanner product.
Please let us know if you’re interested in getting your project hosted!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing</title>
      <link>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/contributing/</guid>
      <description>We’d love to accept your patches and contributions! For details, please check the README.md and docs/contributing.md files in the repository of the project that you’re interested in.
Please get in touch if you’re interested in starting a new project or moving an existing repository to this organization! All projects hosted here need to have good test coverage. We’re happy to help you with setting up unit and integration tests, but we rely on your contributions for continued maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Open Source Community Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>At Google, we recognize and celebrate the creativity and collaboration of open source contributors and the diversity of skills, experiences, cultures, and opinions they bring to the projects and communities they participate in.
Every one of Google&amp;rsquo;s open source projects and communities are inclusive environments, based on treating all individuals respectfully, regardless of gender identity and expression, sexual orientation, disabilities, neurodiversity, physical appearance, body size, ethnicity, nationality, race, age, religion, or similar personal characteristic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/projects/</guid>
      <description>App Engine Java Sample demonstrates how to use Cloud Spanner from the App Engine Standard with Java 11 environment.
  Autoscaler is a companion tool to Cloud Spanner that allows you to automatically increase or reduce the number of nodes in one or more Spanner instances, based on their utilization.
  HarbourBridge is a stand-alone tool for Cloud Spanner evaluation, using data from an existing PostgreSQL database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudspannerecosystem.dev/resources/</guid>
      <description>Talks  Cloud Spanner 101: Google&amp;rsquo;s mission-critical relational database Spanner Internals Part 1: What Makes Spanner Tick? Spanner Internals Part 2: Global Meta-Data and Scalable Data Backend Best Practices on Migrating to Cloud Spanner Ben Sigelman presents the Spanner whitepaper  Podcasts  Google Cloud Platform Podcast Software Engineering Daily The Architect  Meetups  Google Cloud Spanner Developers, San Francisco, CA  Documentation  Official Documentation Best Practices API Reference GCP Weekly: Spanner  Whitepapers  Spanner: Google&amp;rsquo;s Globally-Distributed Database Spanner, TrueTime and the CAP Theorem Spanner: Becoming a SQL System  Libraries and ORMs Client libraries  Authentication via Application Default Credentials (ADC) Java (tutorial) Go (tutorial) Node.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
